Guide to the Church Coalition for Human Rights in the Philippines records, 1982-1993.
Church Coalition for Human Rights in the Philippines records
- International Ecumenical Conference on the Philippines-1983, 1983 (Box 15)
- INFOS 1985, 1985 (Box 15)
- Philippine Joing Action Group - 1987, 1987 (Box 15)
- Philippine Joing Action Group - 1988, 1988 (Box 15)
- Philippine Joing Action Group - 1989, 1989 (Box 15)
- Philippine Joing Action Group - 1990, 1990 (Box 15)
- Philippine Joing Action Group - 1991 and packet 1991-92, 1991-1992 (Box 15)
- Philippine Joing Action Group - 1992, 1992 (Box 15)
- Philippine Joing Action Group - 1993, 1993 (Box 15)
- Philippine Joing Action Group - 1994, 1994 (Box 15)
- NCC-EAP and PJAG Meetings, Date unknown (Box 15)
- People's Congress 1992, 1992 (Box 15)
- Miscellaneous publications, Date unknown (Box 15)
- Snap Revolution, Date unknown (Box 16)
  Newspaper Clippings
- Snap Election, Date unknown (Box 16)
- Hidden Wealth, Date unknown (Box 16)
- Peace Talks/Ceasefire Rebels, Date unknown (Box 16)
- Enrile; Military Coup, Right Wing Cabinet split, Date unknown (Box 16)
- OLALIA, Alay-ay Murder, Date unknown (Box 16)
- Marcos Wealth Loyalists, Date unknown (Box 16)
- Aquino US Visit. AID. Japan Visit, Date unknown (Box 16)
- Muslims, Date unknown (Box 16)
- Constitution, US Bases Nuclear Free Program, Date unknown (Box 16)
- Economy Farmers Labor, Date unknown (Box 16)
- IRD/Church attacked Fr. Ed Visa, Church and State, Date unknown (Box 16)
- Miscellaneous, Date unknown (Box 16)
- Human Rights Summary Reports 1989-1992, 1989-1992 (Box 16)
- AIDS in the US Bases, Date unknown (Box 17)
- Cory's 1000 Days, Date unknown (Box 17)
- Aquino Assassination/Investigation, Date unknown (Box 17)
- Aquino Administration, Date unknown (Box 17)
- Asian Development Bank, Date unknown (Box 17)
- US Bases: Editorial Arguments Against, Date unknown (Box 17)
- US Bases: 1988 re-negotiation with RP, 1988 (Box 17)
- US Bases: Nuclear Weapons Debate, Date unknown (Box 17)
- US Bases: Labor Socio-econ. Effects (prostitution) and alternatives, Date unknown (Box 17)
- US Bases: killing of 3 American Servicemen, Date unknown (Box 17)
- Bases campaign, Date unknown (Box 17)
- NFIP Conference - Tanada speech, Date unknown (Box 17)
- Gorbachev Initiative (Conm Ranh Bay), Date unknown (Box 17)
- Cartoons, Date unknown (Box 17)
- Cartoons in the Philippines, Date unknown (Box 17)
- Children, Date unknown (Box 17)
- Cease-fire, Date unknown (Box 17)
- Philippine Church, Date unknown (Box 17)
- Communist Party of the Philippines (CPP), Date unknown (Box 17)
- (Philippine) Congress, Date unknown (Box 17)
- (Philippine) Congress - House, Date unknown (Box 17)
- Constitution, Date unknown (Box 17)
- Cordillera Autonomy/Balweg/CPLA, Date unknown (Box 17)
- Counter insurgency, Date unknown (Box 17)
- Coup Jan. 1987, 1987-01 (Box 17)
- August 28, 1987 Coup, 1987-08-28 (Box 17)
- Coup Attempts - General Post - August 1987, 1987-08 (Box 17)
- Countering insurgency - CAFGU, Date unknown (Box 17)
- Post August 28 Cabinet Reorganization, Date unknown (Box 17)
- CPLA, Date unknown (Box 17)
- Cronies - Marcos, Date unknown (Box 17)
- Debt, Date unknown (Box 17)
- Economy, Date unknown (Box 17)
- (Phil) Domestic Helpers, Date unknown (Box 17)
- Environment/Ecology, Date unknown (Box 17)
- Environmental Concerns, Date unknown (Box 17)
- Education, Date unknown (Box 17)
- 2nd EDSA Anniversary Statements, Date unknown (Box 17)
- May Elections, Date unknown (Box 17)
- January Local Elections, Date unknown (Box 17)
- Filipina as Domestic (Women), Date unknown (Box 17)
- Ferry sinly Dec 21 and Oct 24 1988, 1988-10-24-1988-12-21 (Box 17)
- FFM, Date unknown (Box 17)
- Filipino in the US, Date unknown (Box 17)
- Foreigners in Philippines, Date unknown (Box 17)
- (Empty Folder) Anti-Nuke, Date unknown (Box 17)
- Foreign Intervention, Date unknown (Box 17)
- Government Officials, Date unknown (Box 17)
- Graft and Corruption, Date unknown (Box 17)
- Hostage Swap, Date unknown (Box 17)
- Health, Date unknown (Box 17)
- Human Rights, Date unknown (Box 17)
- Iran-Contra, Date unknown (Box 17)
- Japan, Date unknown (Box 17)
- Judiciary, Date unknown (Box 17)
- Land Reform, Date unknown (Box 18)
- Land Distribution, Date unknown (Box 18)
- Labor, Date unknown (Box 18)
- Labor-Human Rights Violations, Date unknown (Box 18)
- Low Intensity Conflict, Date unknown (Box 18)
- Marcoses, Date unknown (Box 18)
- Marcos' Wealth, Date unknown (Box 18)
- Middle Class - Philippines, Date unknown (Box 18)
- MNLF, Date unknown (Box 18)
- Marcos Loyalist, Date unknown (Box 18)
- Media, Date unknown (Box 18)
- Media - Articles published by CCHRP Network, Date unknown (Box 18)
- Mendiola Massacre, Date unknown (Box 18)
- Militarization, Date unknown (Box 18)
- Miscellaneous, Date unknown (Box 18)
- Military (Philippine), Date unknown (Box 18)
- Military Conflict, Date unknown (Box 18)
- National Democratic Front, Date unknown (Box 18)
- NDF, Date unknown (Box 18)
- Nat Situationer, Date unknown (Box 18)
- Bello articles and reaction, Date unknown (Box 18)
- NPA, Date unknown (Box 18)
- NPA - "Sparrows", Date unknown (Box 18)
- News Letters, Date unknown (Box 18)
- Nuke Issues in Phil., Date unknown (Box 18)
- Peace Talks, Date unknown (Box 18)
- Philippine Gov't - Brune, Date unknown (Box 18)
- Philippine Gov't - Malaysa, Date unknown (Box 18)
- (name?) Peoples Maos Organizations, Date unknown (Box 18)
- PKP, Date unknown (Box 18)
- Pharmaceutical Industry, Date unknown (Box 18)
- Philippine Culture, Date unknown (Box 18)
- Philippine Gov't - Foreign Relations, Date unknown (Box 18)
- Political Parties - Philippines, Date unknown (Box 18)
- Population, Date unknown (Box 18)
- Population, Date unknown (Box 18)
- Poverty, Date unknown (Box 18)
- Prostitution/Sex Syndicates, Date unknown (Box 18)
- Prostitution - Child Prostitution, Date unknown (Box 18)
- Refugees, Date unknown (Box 18)
- Right Wing Opposition (within the Philippines), Date unknown (Box 18)
- Rural Development, Date unknown (Box 18)
- Schultz's Visit - June 1987, 1987-06 (Box 18)
- Philippine Senate, Date unknown (Box 18)
- Student Activists, Date unknown (Box 18)
- Soviet Union, Date unknown (Box 18)
- Tasaday, Date unknown (Box 18)
- Transnational Corporations, Date unknown (Box 18)
- Transportation, Date unknown (Box 18)
- US Aid, Date unknown (Box 18)
- Mini-Marshall Plan, Date unknown (Box 18)
- US Philippine Relations, Date unknown (Box 18)
- US Intervention, Date unknown (Box 18)
- US Intervention "Gold Hunters", Date unknown (Box 18)
- US Intervention Right Wing Groups, Date unknown (Box 18)
- Urban Poor, Date unknown (Box 18)
- Vigilantes, Date unknown (Box 18)
- Vigilantes - Alsa Masa, Date unknown (Box 18)
- Vigilantes, Date unknown (Box 18)
- Vigilantes/Right Wing, Date unknown (Box 18)
- Women, Date unknown (Box 18)
- World Bank, Date unknown (Box 18)
- Untitled, Date unknown (Box 18)
- Philippine Politics, Date unknown (Box 18)
- Presidential Election, Date unknown (Box 18)
- Kabisig, Date unknown (Box 18)
- Strategies and Operations, Date unknown (Box 18)
- Counter-Insurgency: Strategies, LIC, Date unknown (Box 18)
- Armed Forces of the Philippines, Date unknown (Box 18)
- YOU, Date unknown (Box 18)
- Paramilitary/Vigilantes, Date unknown (Box 18)
- US Phil. Relations, Date unknown (Box 18)
- Philippine Situationers, Date unknown (Box 18)
- The Washington Post Clippings, 1990, 1990 (Box 18)
- 1989 Extension, 1989 (Box 18)
- Graphics, Date unknown (Box 18)
- Other Org Campaigns, Date unknown (Box 18)
- Letters to the Editor, Date unknown (Box 18)
- Gereral Coor, Date unknown (Box 18)
- Correspondence, Date unknown (Box 18)
- Untitled, Date unknown (Box 18)
- Emer. Powers Bill/Law Post-Cpop 1989, 1989 (Box 18)
- Post-Coup Clipping 1989, 1989 (Box 18)
- Press Freed during Emer. Power 1989, 1989 (Box 18)
- 1989 December Coup (RAM) Church Statements, 1989-12 (Box 18)
- Post Coup State of Emergency, Date unknown (Box 18)
- 1989 December Coup (RAM): Clippings, 1989 (Box 18)
- 1989 December Coup (RAM): Clippings, 1989 (Box 18)
- 1989 December Coup (RAM): Notes, 1989 (Box 18)
- Benigno Aquino Assassination, Date unknown (Box 19)
- CAMIP Literature, Date unknown (Box 19)
- Development and Economy, Date unknown (Box 19)
- Economy, Date unknown (Box 19)
- Agrarian Reform, Date unknown (Box 19)
- CAMIP, Date unknown (Box 19)
- Chico River Dam Project, Date unknown (Box 19)
- Rop Stark Cong Record, Date unknown (Box 19)
- Consequences of Nuclear Attack on the Philippines - J Emmanuel, Date unknown (Box 19)
- Nat. Conf. on May 14 elections, April 15, 1984, 1984-04-15 (Box 19)
- Extradition Treaty and Campaign against it, Date unknown (Box 19)
- MNLF, Date unknown (Box 19)
- NPA, Date unknown (Box 19)
- Bangsa Moro News Maharoika, Date unknown (Box 19)
- Miscellaneous, Date unknown (Box 19)
- Prisoners List, Date unknown (Box 20)
- Prisoner - other campaigns, Date unknown (Box 20)
- Church Workers, Date unknown (Box 20)
- Correspondance, Date unknown (Box 20)
- Christmas 1984, 1984 (Box 20)
- Prisoner Mater., Date unknown (Box 20)
- Families Fleeing War, Date unknown (Box 20)
- Reports from US writers, Date unknown (Box 20)
- US Refugee Groups, Date unknown (Box 20)
- Cafgus a Vigilantes, Date unknown (Box 20)
- CCHRP Action: Church Persecution, Date unknown (Box 20)
- 1989 PCPR Summary: Ch. Persecution, 1989 (Box 20)
- Editorials Church Persecution, Date unknown (Box 20)
- US media: Church Persecution, Date unknown (Box 20)
- Attack of TFD, Date unknown (Box 20)
- Statements, Date unknown (Box 20)
- TFD - Demerul award, Date unknown (Box 20)
- APC HR Network, Date unknown (Box 20)
- Asia Watch, Date unknown (Box 20)
- Amnesty Anteinational, Date unknown (Box 20)
- PAHRA, Date unknown (Box 20)
- Report on Nat. Endowment for Democracy…AFL-CIO, Date unknown (Box 20)
- Education, Date unknown (Box 20)
- Educational Packets, Date unknown (Box 20)
- Mission Study Resources, Date unknown (Box 20)
- Anti-Communist Crusade 1988, 1988 (Box 20)
- Militarization/Nat. Security, Date unknown (Box 20)
- Singlaub, Date unknown (Box 20)
- Aquino Govt. (Economic Policy), Date unknown (Box 20)
- Aquino Govt (Human rights), Date unknown (Box 20)
- US Philippine Relations (Economic), Date unknown (Box 20)
- Philippine Economy, Date unknown (Box 20)
- Economy-Business Outlook-1985, 1985 (Box 20)
- 1987 - EPIC - Background Materials, 1987 (Box 20)
- Church Persecution, Date unknown (Box 20)
- Amanda Doromila, Date unknown (Box 20)
- Church, Date unknown (Box 20)
- AIDS 1986, 1986 (Box 20)
- Washington Post Articles - 1987, 1987 (Box 20)
- Santa Fe Documents, Date unknown (Box 20)
- "Sovient interests" 1981, 1981 (Box 20)
- TNC's, Date unknown (Box 20)
- The Philippines under President Cory Aquino, Date unknown (Box 20)
- National Situation/Analysis, Date unknown (Box 21)
- US Bases in the Philippines - Primary materials, Date unknown (Box 21)
- On Church, Date unknown (Box 21)
- Basic Information on the Philippines, Date unknown (Box 21)
- Sector: Progressive Church - Folder 2, Date unknown (Box 21)
- Bangsa Moro Struggle - Folder 1, Date unknown (Box 21)
- Bangsa Moro Struggle - Folder 2, Date unknown (Box 21)
- US Crisis, Date unknown (Box 21)
- Philippines: Key Documents, Date unknown (Box 21)
- Maps, Date unknown (Box 21)
- Political Economy, Date unknown (Box 21)
- IMF - WB/Philippine Debt, Date unknown (Box 21)
- TNC and Foreign Interests, Date unknown (Box 21)
- Analysis - National Situationers: Primary Resources 1987-1988, 1987-1988 (Box 21)
- Analysis - State of the Nation 1986-1988, 1986-1988 (Box 21)
- On Land Reform, Date unknown (Box 21)
- US Bases in the Philippines - Articles/Annot. Bib., Date unknown (Box 21)
- US Intervention - General, Date unknown (Box 21)
- The Religious Right - Philippine-Based, Date unknown (Box 21)
- The Religious Right - US Based, Date unknown (Box 21)
- Low Intensity Conflict - US and CA Based, Date unknown (Box 21)
- Low Intensity Conflict - Philippine Based, Date unknown (Box 21)
- Vigilantes, Date unknown (Box 21)
- HR/US Intervention, Date unknown (Box 21)
- Human Rights - Conceptual/Technical, Date unknown (Box 21)
- Human Rights - Stats Documentations, Org., Date unknown (Box 21)
- Human Rights - Supplementary Subjects, Date unknown (Box 21)
- Human Rights - FF Reports/Reflections, Date unknown (Box 21)
- Human Rights - Publications, Date unknown (Box 21)
- Church Repression in the Philippines, Date unknown (Box 21)
- Basic Christian Communities - BCC-CO, Date unknown (Box 21)
- Regional Report - Mindanao, Date unknown (Box 21)
- Regional Report - Mindanao HR, Date unknown (Box 21)
- Regional Report - Negros (esp Workers), Date unknown (Box 21)
- Regional Report - Negros HR, Date unknown (Box 21)
- Sectoral Concerns, Date unknown (Box 21)
- Sector: Labour Situationers/Other Info, Date unknown (Box 21)
- Sector - Peasants, Date unknown (Box 21)
- Sector - Women Organizations/Publications, Date unknown (Box 21)
- Sector - Women Situationers and Orientations, Date unknown (Box 21)
- Sector: Women Migrant Wkrs/Health/women and church, Date unknown (Box 21)
- Sector: Women on Violence and Trafficking, Date unknown (Box 21)
- Regional Reports - CL Profile/NL Situationer GE, Date unknown (Box 21)
- Regional Report - NL/Cordillera HR, Date unknown (Box 21)
- Sector - Women Workers, Date unknown (Box 21)
- Sector - Progressive Church Folder 1, Date unknown (Box 21)
- Sector - Education and Culture, Date unknown (Box 21)
- Miscellaneous Clippings/Sectors, Date unknown (Box 21)
- Sector - Health, Date unknown (Box 21)
- Cordillera - People's Development/Foreign Interests, Date unknown (Box 21)
- Environmental Concerns - Cordillera, Date unknown (Box 21)
- Case of Alfonso Surigao Jr., human rights lawyer, Date unknown (Box 21)
- Letters to the Editor, Date unknown (Box 22)
- Ferdinand Marcos, Date unknown (Box 22)
- Drugs, …next folder: COORESP, Date unknown (Box 22)
- Davao Hostage Crisis, Date unknown (Box 22)
- US Bases, Date unknown (Box 22)
- Human Rights Asia, Date unknown (Box 22)
- Southeast Asia Politics, Date unknown (Box 22)
- Education, Date unknown (Box 22)
- Land Reform, Date unknown (Box 22)
- National Democratic Front, Date unknown (Box 22)
- NGO, Date unknown (Box 22)
- NPA-Editorials, Date unknown (Box 22)
- 1992 Pres. Elections, 1992 (Box 22)
- Peace, Date unknown (Box 22)
- Personalities, Date unknown (Box 22)
- YOU (Young Officers Union), Date unknown (Box 22)
- Paramilitary Groups/Vigilantes, Date unknown (Box 22)
- Philippines Politics (elections, parties, personalities), Date unknown (Box 22)
- US Philippine Relations (Peace Corp abduct'n/US intervention), Date unknown (Box 22)
- Strategies and Operations (Anti-communism, CPP), Date unknown (Box 22)
- Counter-Insurgency Strategies (Total war/low intensity conflict), Date unknown (Box 22)
- Philippine Situationers, Date unknown (Box 22)
- Philippine Gov't (congress, judiciary, courts, local gov't), Date unknown (Box 22)
- Poverty, Date unknown (Box 22)
- Armed Forces of the Philip. (Plaza Miranda bombing, AFP/NPA), Date unknown (Box 22)
- Development and Environment, Date unknown (Box 22)
- Economy (inflation, debt, internat. Trade, MAI/PAP, wages, IMF), Date unknown (Box 22)
- AID, Date unknown (Box 22)
- Aquino Assessment, Date unknown (Box 22)
- Church and Religion, Date unknown (Box 22)
- Demographics and Geography (empty folder), Date unknown (Box 22)
- Children, Date unknown (Box 22)
- Pamphlets, Date unknown (Box 22)
- Aquino Assessment, 1989 (Box 23)
- Children, 1989 (Box 23)
- Church and Religion, 1989 (Box 23)
- Development and Environment: Agriculture and Health, 1989 (Box 23)
- IMF, 1989 (Box 23)
- 1989 December Coup (RAM) Analysis Documents, 1989-12 (Box 23)
- 1989 December Coup cabinet revamp, 1989-12 (Box 23)
- 1989 December Coup editorials, 1989-12 (Box 23)
- 1989 December Coup government posture, 1989-12 (Box 23)
- 1989 December Coup institutional church response, 1989-12 (Box 23)
- 1989 December Coup military analysis, 1989-12 (Box 23)
- 1989 December Coup military post-coup reforms, 1989-12 (Box 23)
- 1989 December Coup personalities, 1989-12 (Box 23)
- 1989 December Coup statements, 1989-12 (Box 23)
- 1989 December Coup: US intervention, 1989-12 (Box 23)
- 1989 December Coup: US press coverage, 1989-12 (Box 23)
- 1989 December Coup: miscellaneous, 1989-12 (Box 23)
- State visit to the USA of Corzan Aquino Nov 7-11, 1989, 11/7/1989-1989-11-11 (Box 23)
- Earthquakes 1990, 1990 (Box 23)
- Economy, 1990 (Box 23)
- Education, 1990 (Box 23)
- Foreign Aid, 1990 (Box 23)
- Health, 1990 (Box 23)
- Land Reform, 1990 (Box 23)
- Peace, 1990 (Box 23)
- Karl Gaspar, and Florencia Abad, 1990 (Box 23)
- Poverty, 1990 (Box 23)
- NDF, 1990 (Box 23)
- NPA Editorial/News, 1990 (Box 23)
- Aid, 1991 (Box 23)
- Aquino Assessment, 1991 (Box 23)
- Church and Religion, 1991 (Box 23)
- Development and the Environment, 1991 (Box 23)
- Economy, 1991 (Box 23)
- Foreign Aid, 1991 (Box 23)
- Land Reform, 1991 (Box 23)
- NDA, 1991 (Box 23)
- NPA, 1991 (Box 23)
- Peace, 1991 (Box 23)
- Philippine Politics, 1991 (Box 23)
- Philippine Situationer, 1991 (Box 23)
- US Gov't Documents, 1991 (Box 23)
- RAM/YOU, 1991 (Box 23)
- Philippines and The Gulf War 1991, 1991 (Box 23)
- Mt. Pinatubo, 1991 (Box 23)
- Poverty in the Country, 1991 (Box 23)
- RP - US Relations, 1991 (Box 23)
- Strategies and Operations, 1991 (Box 23)
- Armed Forces of the Philippines, 1991 (Box 23)
- The Washington Post Clippings, 1991 (Box 23)
- Leyte Floods, 1991 (Box 23)
- Clippings from RP 1991, 1991 (Box 23)
- NECP, Date unknown (Box 24)
- BNPP: Bataan Nuclear Plant, Date unknown (Box 24)
- Debt: General, Date unknown (Box 24)
- Steering Committee, Date unknown (Box 24)
- Misc., Date unknown (Box 24)
- PDF: Debt Action Group, Date unknown (Box 24)
- Philippine Debt, Date unknown (Box 24)
- PHRL: 1992 (Minutes, Notes, etc), 1992 (Box 24)
- NECP-CCC, Date unknown (Box 24)
- Urgent Actions, Date unknown (Box 24)
- Newspaper Clippings and handouts, Date unknown (Box 24)
- Peace Process 93, 1993 (Box 24)
- Labor 93, 1993 (Box 24)
- 1993 Newspaper Clippings, 1993 (Box 24)
- Ramos Emergency Powers, Date unknown (Box 24)
- Reimposition of Death Penalty 93, 1993 (Box 24)
- (Newspaper clippings) 2 folders, Date unknown (Box 24)
- Post-Election Analysis 92, 1993 (Box 24)
- Church and the Elections 92, 1993 (Box 24)
- Elections 92, 1993 (Box 24)
- Women, 1993 (Box 24)
- Women workers, 1993 (Box 24)
- Tribal filipinos, 1993 (Box 24)
- Fishermen and Women, 1993 (Box 24)
- MORO, 1993 (Box 24)
- (undesignated, unlabelled folder), 1993 (Box 24)
- Teachers, 1993 (Box 24)
- Students, 1993 (Box 24)
- Sugar Workers, 1993 (Box 24)
- Urban Poor, 1993 (Box 24)
- Welgang Bayan October 26-29, 1990, 1990-10-26-1990-10-29 (Box 24)
- Welgang Bayan October 1990, 1990 (Box 24)
- MEDIA, Date unknown (Box 25)
- Overseas/Migrant Workers, Date unknown (Box 25)
- Transport workers, Date unknown (Box 25)
- (unlabelled folder), Date unknown (Box 25)
- Urban Poor, Date unknown (Box 25)
- Youth and Students, Date unknown (Box 25)
- Tribal filipinos, Date unknown (Box 25)
- Farmers, Date unknown (Box 25)
- Health Workers, Date unknown (Box 25)
- Labor, Date unknown (Box 25)
- TEACHERS, Date unknown (Box 25)
- Labor Kaibigan Update 1990, 1990 (Box 25)
- Kanlungan ng Migrante, Date unknown (Box 25)
- Link NFWS-FGT - Negros 1990-1992, 1990-1992 (Box 25)
- Parent's Alternative Inc., "The Filipino child's link", Date unknown (Box 25)
- Philippine Migration Review, Date unknown (Box 25)
- Philippine Trade Union Report, Date unknown (Box 25)
- Ramos on Peace, Date unknown (Box 25)
- Yawos Silatan, Date unknown (Box 25)
- US Clippings October 1985, 1985 (Box 25)
- General Ramos, Date unknown (Box 25)
- Originals of Philippine Info Packet for the Ecumenical conference 1983, 1983 (Box 25)
- Basic Education Packet (file copies), Date unknown (Box 25)
- Philippines Information Packet, Date unknown (Box 25)
- (Newspaper/magazine clippings), Date unknown (Box 25)
- Church Persecution, Date unknown (Box 25)
- Human Rights Situation A-I, Date unknown (Box 25)
- Media, Date unknown (Box 25)
- Miscellaneous Sheets, Date unknown (Box 25)
- Slide Show - General Info, Date unknown (Box 25)
- 1987 Packet from Philippines HR and General Situation, 1987 (Box 25)
- Church workers, Date unknown (Box 25)
- Anti Bases Campaign in US, Date unknown (Box 25)
- Negros/Hunger 1985, 1985 (Box 25)
- Miscellaneous materials, Date unknown (Box 25)
- Program Development, Date unknown (Box 25)
  News clippings
- 1993 News Clippings, 1993 (Box 25)
- Vigilantes/LIC 1987, 1987 (Box 26)
- Military in Torture Cases, Date unknown (Box 26)
- US Lawyer's Report, Date unknown (Box 26)
- Notes on Fely Carino's paper on Theology of Struggle, Date unknown (Box 26)
- Right Wing: Singlaub CIA, Date unknown (Box 26)
- Ruth M. Harris, Date unknown (Box 26)
- Walden Bello, Date unknown (Box 26)
- Commission on Integrated Long-Term Strategy, Date unknown (Box 26)
- Presidential Letter, Date unknown (Box 26)
- US Bases, Date unknown (Box 26)
- Human Rights Statistics, Date unknown (Box 26)
- World Council of Churches International Affairs Commission, Date unknown (Box 26)
- US Philippino Relations Bello articles, Date unknown (Box 26)
- CCHRP Updates 1982, 1982 (Box 26)
- Washington Post Letters to the Editor (October 1986 controversy re: William Branigin article), 1986-10 (Box 26)
- Peace Campaign 1987, 1987 (Box 26)
- Kairos Project, Date unknown (Box 26)
- Letter of Concern, Date unknown (Box 26)
- Fund For Open Information and Accountability, Inc, Date unknown (Box 26)
- Background of Philippines, Date unknown (Box 26)
- Counter Insurgency, CIA: UN National Sec., Date unknown (Box 26)
- CIA, Date unknown (Box 26)
- Covert Operations, Date unknown (Box 26)
- Damuscus Document, Date unknown (Box 26)
- Mindanao, Date unknown (Box 26)
- Newsweek/Time/Asia Week Articles on the Philippines, Date unknown (Box 26)
- Ciodillera/NL HRO, Date unknown (Box 26)
- Philippine Miscellaneous Articles, Date unknown (Box 26)
- Miscellaneous unsorted materials, Date unknown (Box 26)
- News clippings 1992 (in binder), 1982 (Box 27)
- News clippings 1989 (in binder), 1989 (Box 27)
- Miscellaneous unsorted documents, Date unknown (Box 27)
- World Bank Reports, Date unknown (Box 27)
- Boycott May 14, 1984 elections, 1984 (Box 27)
- Congressional Hearing (Testimonies) 11/18/81, 1981-11-18 (Box 27)
- Assoc. of Major Religious Superiors: Various Reports, Date unknown (Box 27)
- Ibon, Date unknown (Box 27)
- Methodists make news, Date unknown (Box 28)
- Unlabeled folder, Date unknown (Box 28)
- CAMIP accounts, Date unknown (Box 28)
- Unlabeled folder, Date unknown (Box 28)
- Unlabeled folder, Date unknown (Box 28)
- Unlabeled folder, Date unknown (Box 28)
- Bases packet, Date unknown (Box 28)
- Unlabeled folder, Date unknown (Box 28)
- Petition form: bases campaign, Date unknown (Box 28)
- 1987 packet from Philippines: HR and general situation, 1987 (Box 28)
- News reports - Phil., Date unknown (Box 28)
- Church Situationer/CONTAK, Date unknown (Box 28)
- RCPC - HK press, Date unknown (Box 28)
- Foreign control of the economy, Date unknown (Box 28)
- Church workers and government repression, Date unknown (Box 28)
- Media and journalists, Date unknown (Box 28)
- Martial law and strong man rule, Date unknown (Box 28)
- Arbitrary arrests and denial of constitutional rights, Date unknown (Box 28)
- Militarization/hamletting, Date unknown (Box 28)
- Organization of slum dwellers, Date unknown (Box 28)
- US foreign policy in the Philippines, Date unknown (Box 28)
- Aid to Marcos government, Date unknown (Box 28)
- News clippings: 1982, 1982 (Box 28)
- Current news clippings, Date unknown (Box 28)
- Unlabeled folder, Date unknown (Box 28)
- Task force Detainees - Mindanao: 1986, 1st quarter, 1986 (Box 28)
- Miscellaneous unsorted materials, Date unknown (Box 28)
- Book reviews, Date unknown (Box 29)